question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Did Michael Jackson invent the moonwalk?",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
]
